(Leonard:)And for those of you
who were popular in high school,
(Leonard:)it's over, sorry.
(Leonard:)Thank you and congratulations.
TECH SUPPORT (recording):
Your call is important to us.
(Tech Support Voice:)All our technicians are busy
helping other customers.
(Tech Support Voice:)Please stay on the line
(Tech Support Voice:)and someone will be
with you shortly.
(flute music playing)
(Howard:)What happened to me?
(Howard:)When did I become
an old man
(Howard:)baffled by modern
technology?
(Howard:)Next thing you know,
(Howard:)I'll be hitching my pants
up to my armpits
(Howard:)and complaining about
(Howard:)the awful music
the kids are listening to.
It is awful, isn't it?
(Sheldon:)Listen to that noise.